LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
This type of outcome
isn't like you at all.
I have nothing to say.
It was still too early to test rookies
in a real combat situation.
Why not try to put Yano-kun's
memories into a cyberbrain?
Wouldn't he revive?
Ghosts cannot be reproduced.
Even if you copy memories,
the old ghost wouldn't inhabit them.
If we are just trying to maintain Section 9,
we may not need new members.
However, considering how
things might be in the future,
we must find a safe way to train recruits.
That's true,
but I'm still removing Azuma from this operation.
Very well.
Please treat him with respect.
Thanks.
Turmoil at the
Northern Extremity
This information came from an old friend of mine.
A former Russian army officer, Boris
Jablov, who has now turned mafioso,
and several of his men have
taken plutonium out of Russia
into Ostrov Iturup.
So you think Kuze intends to buy that plutonium?
You think he's going nuclear to
declare an independent state?
That's not like him; it's too rash.
One of Kuze's cyborgs killed the agent
who was conducting the investigation.
At the moment, we don't know where he is.
It's been two hours since the agent was killed.
What now?
It's not like we have any choices left, though.
That's true.
So, how will we figure out
the location of the plutonium?
Rushing over to Ostrov Iturup without
a clue isn't going to do any good.
There may be a hint in the
information we got from Public Safety.
It seems Sagawa Electronics
is expanding the Bertalrek underground
factory without permission.
Bertalrek...
Where the Russian submarine base
was located in Ostrov Iturup?
If I recall correctly,
before withdrawing, the Russian military
detonated the base and buried it.
That is correct.
If Sagawa's construction has
been going smoothly since then,
they should have reached the base by now.
I see.
It's suspect, all right.
A submarine base would be an ideal
location to hide a camouflaged ship.
But there is no proof.
If there is a deal that big being planned,
the local informants will have got wind of it.
Chief, we'll go straight
to Ostrov Iturup from here.
Please ask the Coast Guard to
lock down Dejima, just in case.
If the refugees go nuclear,
everything's going to fly apart.
Very well.
I have faith in all of you.
If we do not get Kuze now,
the things the Cabinet
Intelligence Agency has done
will fade into the background.
and the military will intervene.
We must not let Dejima turn into a war zone.
Houeimaru
How was it?
It's fine.
There don't seem to be any traps.
We have time until the deal.
Keep watch in shifts and get some rest.
Okay.
Hey, why don't you eat this?
Are you really all right?
It tastes bad.
No, really, it tastes like crap.
I'll have to say something
about this to the Chief.
There's still some time.
Want to test your cyberbrain activity?
I'm fine.
I just got thrown off by
the size of Kuze's delusion.
That's what I don't get.
What kind of delusion does he have, exactly?
Put in exaggerated terms,
world domination, I suppose.
What?!
Talk about a megalomaniac.
You usually wouldn't be
affected by something like that.
Damn it, you look just like
some kid who's met "the one".
Really.
Well, now we know this for sure:
He initially showed symptoms of
the Individual Eleven virus,
but his actions are now fuelled by
qualities and ideas he already had.
Even though his delusion itself is common,
the reason I couldn't laugh it off
was that he truly believes his becoming
a dictator would bring world peace...
or so it seemed to me.
In addition, his adrenaline secretion levels
would be lethal to the average person,
We should already consider Kuze...
to believe himself to be on holy ground.
What do you mean by "holy ground"?
As in, he's turned into a self-proclaimed prophet.
Historically speaking,
such people exhibit unbelievable strength.
Che Guevara, Malcolm X,
and Cassius Clay would be representative examples.
How are they different from Hitler?
In a way, they're the same species,
but ideologically speaking, they're closer
to Gandhi or Martin Luther King, Jr.
The refugees are connected continuously
to Kuze through a network that
has active zoning and filtering,
and they're high on a live feed of his actions.
But they won't influence him and
try to share his consciousness
because they know that the area
beyond his ghostline is a kill zone.
So, it was a close call for me.
Not funny at all.
Ishikawa, Pazu and Bomer: stay here.
Prepare for the possibility that the deal
is taking place in a different location.
Roger.
Die, you militarist.
This is a dangerous place.
Even though it's been returned to Japan,
the friction between the Russians and the
Japanese won't disappear that quickly.
Whoa!
This is a geofront in construction, isn't it?
So that means if we go towards the base in
here, we may be able to find Kuze.
If we're lucky, yeah.
And if we don't?
In that case, we'll just end up face-to-face
with Sagawa's construction workers.
We don't have time to wait
for the Major to contact us.
Houeimaru
What is it?
I came on this ship because I
heard we were going to buy weapons.
But if I'd known that you were
the one leading this operation,
I wouldn't have come here.
I see...
Then you don't have to come
along if you don't want to.
You can go back,
or disappear into the city of Ostrov Iturup.
I won't force you either way.
I'm for the revolution, too.
But it was the legend Densetsu who first
taught us about the revolution.
Now, almost everyone in Dejima
knows about Comrade Kuze,
but almost no one knows your true identity.
That's why I'm not able to convince myself.
I'm still willing to become a suicide bomber,
just like the legend taught us.
How meaningless.
Suicide is just self-gratification.
A revolution cannot exist without ghosts.
That's why I want to know you.
Give me a reason to believe you.
If not...
Well?
The weapon we're trying to
obtain today is plutonium.
I will use it to force the Japanese government
to acknowledge Dejima as an independent nation.
Return what you borrowed!
That's common decency, don't you think?
Get it?!
Looks like your business is booming.
So, what goods do you have
that you can lend people?
Oh, it's you.
So you remember me.
Is the rumour that Chlordane is
still doing business back there...
true?
Of course.
This way, please.
He's as cautious as ever.
Now, this way please.
Togusa, you wait here.
Over there.
You can go back now as well.
In this world, solicitous people aren't liked.
You must have a lot of trouble dealing with her.
If you don't stay friends with her,
you'll regret it.
Chlordane, it's me.
You were helpful in the Nemuro invasion...
Offensive firewall...
He got burned moments ago.
I wonder where he was diving when it happened.
So he was still here.
Still, he must be pretty skilled to have
burned a hacker of Chlordane's calibre.
The way they used an offensive firewall is illegal
under the Confidential Information Protection Act.
There it is.
A floppy?
I can't believe he's using such
outdated media for his external memory.
That agent must've been having
trouble dealing with these.
Sagawa's true ledger, with the real figures.
"On sale: Lemon cake, 20 kilograms."
"Lemon cake"?
"Half a million dollars per
kilo, MAU withdraws from deal."
"Brokers: Sagawa K, BJ.
20 kilograms of lemon cake."
"K takes 40% as retirement pay."
"Buyer introduced by BP."
Just as I speculated, he'd been tapping
into information on the plutonium deal.
Who's Sagawa's "K"?
It must be Northern Special
Division Chief Kagazaki.
He became the middleman and sold the
goods for half a million dollars per kilo.
The seller is Boris Jablov.
The buyer... is "Asian BP"...
the Asian refugees?
Then, that hacker would be...
Seems Kagazaki's share is in yen.
The prepayment is already deposited to Sagawa.
Two hundred forty million yen?
How can the refugees have that kind of money?
Did Kuze get it?
But if so, how...
Still, this helps.
I remember how you said that Sagawa Electronics
was your least favourite Japanese company.
Cabinet Intelligence Agency
Unofficial Investigation Report
I see.
You shouldn't have quit your job
with the Press Agency.
If you hadn't, the Cabinet Intelligence
Agency might have been a better institution.
Ishikawa, the deal is taking place
at the nuclear submarine base.
There is a possibility that the Cabinet
Intelligence Agency is involved this time as well.
What?
There's no time to explain.
Where are Batou and his men?
They've already entered deep water.
Their comm systems are already cut off.
I'll go over right away.
It's almost time. Let's go.
Tell me one more thing!
I've heard that to buy plutonium,
you need at least a quarter million dollars.
What are you going to do about that money?
Are you going to dupe the Russians?
No, we'll pay them.
I have made all normal citizens,
who get rich on the labour of refugees,
donate just a little bit to us,
in order for them to understand our pain.
Well, it's not like you
would understand what I mean.
This is how it works:
the citizens of this country, who remain
unaware of their privileged lifestyles,
have combined total assets in savings
that easily surpass 900 trillion yen.
Of course, they are also
unaware of this amount itself.
Did you know that there is an
amount that doesn't officially exist
within the interest this money generates?
Doesn't officially exist?
Amounts under one yen.
Numbers coming after the decimal point
that normally aren't even
displayed in computer data.
Just by taking that small
amount from online accounts
you get tens of millions per day.
I created a program that would deposit
that amount into my fictional bank.
I prepared the money from there.
The Japanese people have no idea
that their accounts have money
in sums beyond the decimal point.
The banks also now have AIs manage accounts.
Refugees get taxed if they work in Japan,
but they will never be allowed to naturalise.
As for the Japanese,
they don't even notice that the
system is heavily exploiting them
and just consume information that
they find easy to stomach and digest.
Their society's such a fraud.
I would like to enlighten
them about things like this.
Just how much of that money is there?
Roughly,
10 billion 760 million.
This will be the amount we can use as
military funding in our revolution.
Incredible...
Just who are you...?
I'm just a terrorist.
Though right now,
I'm a bit high on heroism.
Stay here...
and make sure this ship can leave at any time.
I'm counting on you.
So this is the contested expansion sector.
Again?
What's happening today?
I sure hope you guys have permission.
Are you the supervisor here?
Hey, you said "again", didn't you?
What do you mean?
Just a while ago,
two of our armour suits went down,
and before that, a suspicious
looking Russian cyborg went down
with two huge suitcases.
Do we have a winner?
Could be.
But why is the GSDF here...
Why is it just you?
Both Jablov and Kagazaki are
being watched by Public Safety.
That's why I came alone.
Let's get this deal over with.
Fine by me.
The record of the deposit to the
specified account is in here.
Confirm it.
I'll go on ahead.
You guys, follow me.
The deal's now final.
Neither of us can confirm what's inside.
Throw down your weapons and come out!
You're under arrest for suspicion
of violating weapons-proliferation
laws and illegal trafficking
of nuclear substances!
Show yourself.
Saitou, something's wrong.
Forget about this place and go get Coyle.
Roger.
Shit!
I'm getting out!
Make sure you get him.
Stop!
Kuze!
Put that down!
Why didn't you open fire immediately?
Is it because you know what this is?
I don't care about that!
I'm aiming for a head shot!
I don't think you'll manage to get it.
Hurry, take the case to the ship.
But...
Go.
Are you shittin' me, you bastard?!
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
(And show the light)
I hear a voice
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.